part of the hustle own man oh I it's
such a pleasure it's such a pleasure man
we're going to be doing some big things
uh with the hustles old magazine so you
know I'm I'm so uh uh I'm so blessed uh
to have you part of the team and you
know uh and and I I and all the stuff
that you're working on even besides the
hustle zone so we'll get into all of
that uh but the
first I always do that welcome to the
hust Zone how are you guys doing tonight
uh this is Ryan Perez AKA RP to God um
owner of pH uh owner of bowai creative
uh where we donate free websites to
entrepreneurs with disabilities we did
stop that program but we are still um
Contin we are still helping um a few of
our clients um with services to help
them uh see their dreams so um I I still
want to thank you know for the last year
all the supporters of that program all
the people that donated websites uh a
big shout out to you guys uh but yeah
I'm back it's been it's been a while
I've been I've been hustling you know
like if I wasn't hustling then I would
be worried uh folks I would not be here
without you guys uh without your love
and support so if you guys want to
continue on that support and continue on
the hustle Zone uh we are selling
T-shirts as I'm wearing right now so
hustle Zone uh. clo and then you can go
to get that tea um and big shout out to
Philip
Woods um uh Philip Woods has been so
helpful in in putting uh the clothing
line together um and we're adding more
stuff we're adding shirts for kids um we
have um lady uh like a lot of ladies
have been buying it you know I I was
like man you know they're just they're
buying they're not even just buying
they're not buying the tank tops they're
buying everything like the hoodies the
tank tops you know like if I had shoes
they would buy the shoe
so thank you ladies for all your love
and support um folks this is the hustle
Zone and if you guys are not aware of
what we are all about uh we tell the
story you know we started this last year
um in April last year it's been a year
since we've been doing the hustle Zone
um and it started off at the 1% jam
session and we started asking people
what their story was now when you look
at everybody's live broadcast everybody
want to know your
story okay so I I I understand I
understand I mean
um do what you got to do but uh you know
we would I'm just I'm playing not saying
that we were the original people to to
ask about the story but you know the
story we've been asking people for their
stories for quite some time now so um we
have a we have a guest here tonight and
I don't know if my guest can hear me can
you hear
me yes yeah CU my mic the other mic the
light just shut off so I I don't know
understand how you're getting the the
the live feed but I just I'm I'm just
checking so we're almost done here but
my guest tonight um he has um officially
confirmed that he's going to be a part
of the hustle Zone
magazine which is real dope um I really
appreciate him he was the first to you
know to get everything like get his
photos in you know his agreements and
and all that because he's a you know he
is 100% a true Hustler and he's a
businessman he knows how to get things
done um you know he's been in business I
would say for about 20 like he's been
doing a Titans Electrical uh Inc uh how
how long have you been in business for
years no this is my six years 6 years
okay I was just checking you know what
I'm saying but so he's been doing uh
Titans electrical he's also a
motivational speaker uh he is a partner
in uh home of the
hustle and uh and then he is Mr Monday
night folks if you guys haven't seen his
his lives you're missing out this guy is
full of energy and let me tell you a
story okay when we were doing K Crystal
Jones you know she she hooked us
up she wanted she said you know I know
this guy named Jason and he definitely
should be someone on on the hustle Zone
like he he should be a part of the
hustle Zone magazine I'm like okay okay
and um so she sets up the appointment
and then that day I had a tooth
AE and my tooth I use turmeric to like
um to to help with the to think and then
I totally forgot that I had the meeting
that day and so when when I when we when
we actually meet my teeth are all yellow
and my tongue all yellow and I was so
embarrassed
and and I'm trying to convince him that
the hustle Zone's about quality and
quality image and whatnot so I'm so glad
that he did say man this guy's a clown
um
so he's been he's been he's been great
he's been great energy
and so I'm so happy to introduce to you
guys uh Jason Daniels how's it going
Jason man it's going great dude uh
thanks for having me on thanks for
putting me on your platform and allowing
me to be part of the hustles Zone man oh
I it's such a pleasure it's such a
pleasure man we're going to be doing
some big things uh with the hustles own
magazine so you know I'm I'm so uh uh
I'm so blessed uh to have you part of
the team and you know uh and I and I I
and all the stuff that you're working on
even besides the hustle zone so we'll
get into all of that uh but the first
thing I want to ask
you and this is the first question that
I ask everybody is what is your story
now we you know not like six years ago
story like begin where you from you know
where's your mom from where are your
parents from like give me the full story
you got my you you you got me for the
whole night
cool man so uh my parents were both born
here in Memphis Tennessee uh my dad got
in the military so I moved around a lot
as a kid man I actually started school
in uh in Germany uh grew up out west
moved back to Memphis when my dad
my family which is kind of crazy now
because I'm the only one in Memphis mys
haveed all my aunts Andes have my
parents have moved and my
brother
wow that's that's crazy so um and do you
miss your family like do you do they
ever come do they ever come and see
you yeah yeah visit my family welled my
brother
ofu
not them
and
tight so um have you always been
entrepreneurial
[Music]
gr
up
learn didn't
know so why like you know where did that
come from I guess like some some kids
cuz I mean I when I was a kid I was
highly motivated to make money but it's
because I didn't have
any but you know in your case like what
was your you know what was holding you
back you would
say they can't hear you okay one second
here can you guys hear him now how about
now guys check volume on Jason y'all
give me a check man can you hear me
now yo yo yo
Mark and
Eddie let's try that waiting for an
update waiting for an update check check
let me just let me
Che they can't hear you they can't hear
you okay one second hold on one
second can you guys hear him now how
about now guys yeah I think we're good
now J y'all give me a check man can you
hear me now so Co sorry about that okay
so folks I apologize uh I guess we'll
have to edit that portion out but
uh but uh so Jason let's let's start
from the beginning okay so the first
question I normally ask people are uh
you know what's your story so begin from
the very
beginning cool yeah so uh my parents
were born here in Memphis
Tennessee uh my dad was actually uh in
the military uh when I was born I was
born in Kentucky um
and we moved around a whole lot as a kid
my dad graad uh my dad retired when I
was 13 years old and upon retirement we
moved back to Memphis so Memphis has
always been my home even though I
started school in Germany and lived out
west this is where we came for Christmas
vacations this was where the where the
family was no matter where we lived um
and now I've lived here for 25 years and
uh man this is home that's awesome so
Jason now um where did you get the
entrepreneurial Spirit
from like I was saying man I think it I
think it's always been inside me it just
took a little while to come out uh I
never really uh knew how to or or maybe
even had the drive to uh to put it to
use um until one day I just did uh now I
was always trying to do my own thing man
I was involved in the music scene and
kind of walk to to the Beat of My Own
Drum uh but it wasn't until my early 30s
when I uh actually started this business
uh grabbed hold of it with both hands
made a decision that uh I was going to
succeed and there was no other option
and uh when you make that statement and
you live by it um then you really don't
have an option you know I was talking to
somebody the other day and I made the
the reference to you know look out at
the Finish Line you know set your vision
and look at it like a Finish Line and
then when you run that race and you're
running towards that Finish Line man
just know that people are going to be
standing on the sidelines throwing
bricks at you and and that's that's life
chunking bricks at you some of them
you're going to dodge and some of them
are going to hit you right in the mouth
man some of them are going to knock
teeth out some are going to hurt but
always keep your mind on that on that uh
on that Finish Line man keep your eyes
on the prize and know that you're going
to cross that finish line and it's
easier to take those hits as you keep
keep moving towards that uh towards that
goal so what but you know not everybody
just falls into a business says Hey I'm
going just going to be a business person
I'm going to start my own electrical
business you know in your case like what
was the you know what was the the thing
that really pushed you to to to do that
and at the time I was uh I was married
my daughter was I believe 5 years
old and man I woke up one night and just
just was convicted man felt I need to do
better there's some there's something
better there's there's got to be a way
for me to provide a better life for my
family this is now my
responsibility and electric work was
what I did so that was what I knew that
was the craft that I felt like I could
put to work uh and do it myself better
than other people were doing it and were
you working for other companies at the
time and you you know um and were you
happy with the situation that you were
in no no no I I was working for other
companies I was not happy uh I was never
happy working for somebody else so I can
look back and see that it wasn't that I
was lazy now I thought I was lazy at the
time but it was just that I was
uninspired to make some you know to
sweat and uh and make somebody else a
ton of money uh especially the way I was
treated you know if I would have been
treated differently then I probably
could have hung in there a little better
but you know the construction world is
uh is it's pretty it's pretty hard man
it's a it's a pretty tough they're tough
on you uh they they treat you like
and uh and and expect you to keep coming
back for more man and that's just not in
me what can you give me an experience
that you had were um and and the reason
why I'm asking because I really want
people to understand you know what
really pushes people into
entrepreneurialism and there's
situations cuz I mean I've worked for
people that I've hate like you know like
I remember there was uh before I started
my business um I was in a situation that
was you know wasn't good for me wasn't
good for them and I was just you know we
were getting to the point where we're
screaming at each other you know like
I'm sitting here I'm like look I want
more because I'm not happy and you know
I don't like the situation I come home
and then you know my you know my ex-
fiance and my child are hearing me yell
because I was so angry you know with my
situation I just hated the fact that you
know I was working for somebody else
like give me a situation where you felt
where it was just like man I have to
start thinking about other other other
means well you know I I probably uh
didn't take the steps properly the last
time I worked for somebody uh which is a
odd uh odd little coincidence because
the man that I worked for last that I
got into it with and uh who fired me I
actually sat down had lunch with him
about a month ago and uh and he's he's
helping me out a little bit here so um
it's crazy how time and and the
situation heals itself but I was on a
project and and and we conversated about
about this I never knew his side of it I
didn't care about his side of it I
thought the boss you know was was rich
and didn't have any problems and and I
was just the just the labor um but I was
carrying a bunch of lights inside a
church I got there early and was
unloading this big truck with a ton of
lights that we were going to have to
hang and after I've been there 20
minutes just hauling lights inside this
church that's when he saw me and so he
thought that I showed up late and was
just trying to kind of sneak in and and
when in actuality I had already went in
set all my stuff down got my work area
set up and then jumped in and started
helping other people you know I saw a
need and and just jumped in and it it
burned me and he wasn't willing to
listen to me tell my side of it now come
back to find out he knew that the lead
guy on the job was going through a
divorce he was drinking on the job they
found him sleeping on the job so it was
high stress for him and now that I'm an
owner I feel his pain so he sat down and
had lunch I could sympathize with where
he was at at that point in time that
point in time I felt like I wasn't being
respected I felt like I wasn't giv a
fair shake and so I walked off that job
and I never worked for anybody else
again wow and how did that like in
during that moment how did that moment
make you feel like what were you feeling
were you enraged were you sad were you
you know like what were the emotions
that you know really because I mean
emotions en energize people whether
you're you're you're you're mad sad
happy but what was said I I took
responsibility not only for myself but
for uh every other electrician in my
city that was tired of being treated the
way that he was treating us and so I
felt like I it was it was on me to go
out and build a company where you didn't
have to be treated like a dog where you
didn't get treated like a number and so
I set out to build something that was
great not only for our
customers but our employees and I think
a lot of people stop there at the
customers they want to treat the
customers great but the employees don't
really matter right and for me man if
you're on my team I love you like my
brother and now I have women working for
me so I love you like my sister um this
is my family these are the people that I
that I'm with all day every day and I
develop uh relationships with them I I
genuinely care for them uh and I believe
they care for me so it's more of a
family setting a family Dynamic than uh
you know the boss cracking the Whip and
uh everybody else running around just
following orders so I really felt like I
could build something that was different
than the options that were presented out
here in the construction world at that
time wow that's that's pretty powerful
man you know you you know you became a
leader you know because you saw a need
to address how people are treated in the
workplace you know that's how you carry
on business buiness you know especially
when you want to bring your business to
another level you have to have good
leadership skills have you always been a
leader like let's let's let's go into
the time machine how were you as a kid
were you that kid that was telling other
kids what to do or were you you know one
of the kids that just went with the
group like how how would you describe
yourself man complete complete opposite
of who I am right now I was probably who
I am right now in my safe space when I
was you know at home or around my
parents parents or whatever but man we
moved around so much that I was never
able to get comfortable and another
thing I started school early I started
kindergarden when I was four um and
that's real cool my parents thought that
I was really smart and they were giving
me a head start and that's all great and
fine until you get into high school and
and the social Dynamic comes into play
you know I was a junior in high school
at 15 years old couldn't drive a car
watching sophomores take their
girlfriends to school in their own ride
so it got awkward in high school um but
up until that point it was cool I was
just I was smart and I leaned on my on
my intelligence but High School it got a
little funny so I got I got kind of
pushed into a little shell um it took a
it took me to get really comfortable
with somebody before I would be myself
um but as I became an adult that that
changed I got comfortable with who I am
and uh and I'm more comfortable now than
I've ever been um so did you did you
have dreams like what as a child like
what were your dreams I wanted to be a
doctor
man I was gonna be a doctor uh and then
you know when uh when when the Bulls
were winning the Championships I was
goingon to be Michael Jordan you know
but unfortunately neither one of those
happened and I became an electrical
contractor now um how did your parents
see you as a kid and how have like you
know their P not perception but you know
you've grown into this human being you
know what's your parents' perceptions of
you man my parents I have the re the
realest conversations with my mom now
today than I ever have in my entire life
and the things that she tells me about
when I was a kid even now like probably
a month ago I probably had the realest
conversation I've ever had with my mom
and it's not because we're not close
it's just we're finally at a point where
we're really good friends and were able
to to go deep and and reflect on
childhood and what that looked like and
and where she could have done some
things different and where I could have
done things different you know we're
just extremely real with each other and
honest and so she she's told me man
she's like I've always known you were
special um you've always walked to the
beat of your own
drum uh you know some of the outfits and
stuff that I would wear when I was a kid
man we look back at pictures and they're
like what in the world were you thinking
um you know so I've I've never really
cared what the what the world thought um
I was going to live my way I was going
to do things my way I just wasn't so
outward about it I wouldn't have put it
in your face back then if there was
Facebook live I probably wouldn't be on
a Facebook live you know stun on them
the way that I am today wow I don't even
believe you but yeah man that that's
that's crazy so um
I I can sympathize with because or or
empathize because I'm an introvert you
know I'm really expressive on camera but
that's probably the only place I'm
expressive if you were to see me in the
grocery store you would see completely
different Ryan because I'd be like hey
what's up how's it going I'd come over
there and Shake you man I'd come over
there and Shake you but I I'm just I
love my alone time and I love my space
and stuff but I'm I'm not that shy but
you know what put like so the pressures
of high school did it was that what put
you in your shell and is there any
specific moments where you could
remember that really put you there and
then what was the moment so this is a
two questions so what was the moment
that put you in the shell and then what
was the moment that brought you out of
the
shell all right
so moving around as a kid man so so out
west I lived in El Paso Texas through my
influential years I think I was 8 till
11 or
12 and and so it was like like fifth
grade to 8th grade then I moved to
Albuquerque New Mexico for nth grade so
you got to think I grew up
around a Hispanic population between
that 8 and 13 when I start listening to
my own music start wearing dressing
myself picking my own clothes developing
my own
personality I was the minority uh I
believe we were you know four or six% uh
White which is not a big deal it doesn't
bother me but that D Dynamic over there
it was heavily uh influenced by
Hispanics um so you know I was listening
to Cypress Hill and and wearing and
wearing Dicky suits and I had my hair
braided down the sides and you know I
had Chuck Taylor and and so that was
just that was how I grew up that was
where I was at that was the space I was
in right and so when I moved from there
to Memphis
Tennessee I was not accepted uh I mov to
South Haven Mississippi which is just
below the state line first and uh you
know took an took an interest in uh in
black women uh in 10th Grade which is
was not accepted at all at this point in
time uh so it kind of got me got me
blackballed from the school um and we
lived there for one year and then we
moved up here uh to a nicer part uh of
the suburbs in Memphis and uh I started
going to school there man and I I did
not dress the part I didn't sound the
part I didn't look the part uh so I just
wasn't accepted you know uh who I was uh
was was shunned uh and and nobody liked
me uh so it kind of pushed me into a
shell man I didn't want to talk to you
if you didn't want to talk to me um and
so I just got I just got quiet and stuck
to myself and that's how that happened
so as far as coming out of my sh
um my early uh early 20s
uh I picked up a knack for rapping and I
started I started rapping I pursued A
hip-hop career for 15 years oh
snap man I'm I'm dope dude I'm dope I
know you don't believe it I have to send
you something well no no no we're gonna
have to get you to rap on on on on the
live here man you can't just say you're
a rapping and not bust some some bars
here but anyway when we went down to 10x
growthcon man uh we I had a I had a
couple beverages man and I was out on
the yacht rapping with a couple of the
guys man um but when when I I I just
kind of grabbed hold of that of that
skill of that gift I had and then I just
kind of jumped right back out in the
world and was like Hey I don't care if
y'all hate me like me whatever y'all
want to do I'm going to come at you like
this and so that was my early 20s uh all
the way up into uh my early 30s um I
pursued uh I pursued music and had a
good time with it man I've met some I've
met some of the greats man um
had some good conversations and and had
a great time in that life but you know
early 30s hit man hanging out at the
clubs till 4 in the morning for the so
the DJ play your record and all that
stuff man I I outgrew that yeah for sure
so uh who what kind of greates did you
meet what kind of greates did I meet man
so I I got to open for uh for Digital
Underground and and you know that was uh
that was a group that introduced Tupac
Shakur to the world whoa and and so so I
got to do the Humpty Dance Wear the
glasses and and kick the burst with them
and actually do the dance in the back
like like Pock did if you go back and
watch the video pox in there doing the
Humpty Dance yeah that's right but the
conversations I got to have with shock g
off stage you know just really who was
Tupac and how was he you know outside of
who we saw and and and getting to know
that uh that intimate side that human
element of this
this person that we all just you know
worshiped at the time you know this this
uh bigger than life uh rapper that that
that just blessed us with this uh crazy
Dynamic getting to really uh learn who
he was behind the scenes and uh when the
cameras weren't on him and when the mic
wasn't in his hand uh that was really
cool um Buster
ROMs uh I opened for tone L um
Outcast um so some some really some
really cool people man one of the
producers that did a bunch of Biggie
stuff is from here in Memphis and uh
actually got him working on some of my
tracks at one point in time wow so so
can can you do me a favor and uh can you
just spit just one bar just so we can
see what
your you can't come on here without
spitting something oh man let me see
who's on here man I don't I don't want
to I don't want to ruin ruin my my image
that I'm presenting now man come on you
know folks this is the hustle Zone and
you know we are who we are please don't
hate on him don't change his brand he is
a phenomenal guy we want to hear you
rap who wants to hear me rap man can we
get some uh some likes some fires some
shares we got going on here let's get
the let's get the people up here
um oh shoot I think I'm okay we got okay
come on give me some some likes
[Laughter]
give me some likes we're at 13 right now
give me some
likes oh we're getting more likes I'm
seeing likes uh oh uh oh oh snap
everybody's throwing the likes on here
so they want to they all the way up yeah
hell
yeah and they're throwing loves they're
throwing loves okay so um okay how many
people we got on here right now man we
have we got nine people on here okay
we're gonna put on we're gonna put on a
concert or what yes we are go
ahead this game is on again I play the
win if not it's not worth engaging in
I'm blazing in rock my hat low so my
blush eyes are here that F within what
keep stand ahead of them at least one
step but probably 10 who you think you
messing with like I ain't going in
that's all you get
buddy that is awesome that is awesome
thank you so much for uh for for for
doing that um pull it out of me man pull
it out well I you know cuz I understand
you know I think um you know me being an
an um introvert I use music as a way for
me to uh express myself so I mean it
always music always helps getting you
you know out of your shell and and
whatnot so I really appreciate you
sharing that story so we're going to cut
to Commercial and then we're going to
we're going to talk
about muted okay so we're back okay
technical difficulties that's why we
love editing okay so uh we're going to
check out the comments make sure you
guys check out the hustle Zone do
clothing purchase your hustle Zone
sweaters purchase your
um
uh what was I going to say putas your
tank tops and and whatnot we need your
support in order for us to give you
better quality every single time uh
we're going to go to the the the
comments here
so Mark says Ryan what's what's up
Mark okay everyone's saying unmute
unmute unmute okay no sound
unmute okay coming back in a
[Music]
minute okay so we're just flipping
through the comments
here Fly Guy Samurai in the house what's
up
Jason Lucky
13 bust the flow bust the flow
me and and and and dougen has told me
you are great me since uh dougen what's
dougen do you know what what
she's Dogan sorry sorry do I'm call you
duing um sorry about that okay so hit
the beat so okay so we're gonna get back
to the the question so we're going to
change up the line of questioning here
um
all kinds of uh technical difficulties
today but you know we're going to we'll
we'll we're going to ride through it
you're going to see more of Jason on the
hustle zone for sure so uh
Jason so tell
me what's your favorite dessert
[Laughter]
oh I love carot cake and cheesecake
cheesecake is my favorite so uh what's
your favorite song right
now
edud
Ed I went saw that guy live at conc a
couple years
ago's
AUD
yeah yeah he looks like some of you
would beat up you know what I mean and
then when you see him and then he starts
dropping you're like yeah like you know
he's pretty groovy like his his and the
the dance hall and all the different
exper you know um influences he has in
his music I think it's dope
erer
thats awesome so
um oh you're oh oh my God what is going
on today we're having a lot of problems
man and this
sucks okay we're back okay so let let me
let let's start this again so what's
your favorite dessert we're getting lots
of practice man oh my God today was one
of those days I tell you it used to be
cheesecake was I thought it was Friday
and and it's acting like Monday right um
used to love cheesecake man till I was
introduced to Gourmet carrot cake man
and Jay Alexander's carrot cake man it's
over dude it's so good so carot cake and
then the the the next question is what
what song you're listening to so
everyone knows what you're talking about
man Ed Sharon's a racer man really Ed
Sharon's new album I'm I'm an ed shearon
fan uh I went and saw him live a couple
years ago and and didn't know what to
expect and uh he came out with just a
guitar and that's it no no band no
nothing just the loop pedal and the
guitar and he crafted all the music all
the drum beats he' made beating on the
guitar and and did it all himself in
cargo shorts and and like douge socks
man the socks that come up to your knees
but you push them down you know he did
look like the like the nerd you know but
that dude is talented man he's got some
skills okay so next is um what would you
tell
your your old
self um now what would you tell them how
old are we talking between in your with
high school
days be you be you man don't be scared
to be yourself walk confidently in
exactly who you are and cut your own
path man don't don't let these uh
Knuckleheads you're running around with
uh steer you away from the vision for
the reason that you're placed here for
your purpose man maximize your potential
and and Chase that
dream what's your biggest dream
now man uh I'm all about touches man I I
am I'm big on touches I want to touch I
want to help I want to help people
maximize their potential and I've got a
bunch of different Avenues to do that I
I do that through my business I do that
through my speaking I'll I'll do that
through my writing um everything that I
do I'm looking
for touches man I I want to I want to
grab people uh somebody who needs uh
whatever content I'm providing I I want
him to grab hold of it and uh and that's
the reason for the transparency man
that's why I try to be just extremely
exposed without putting anybody else on
blast I try to let people know exactly
who I am uh and and the hardships that
come along with being me and where I
fall where I Stumble where I'm weak uh
and also the the victories I mean nobody
wants to see you fall fall fall and not
see you win but you for me man I need to
give you I need to give you the real
which is a good combination of both mhm
do you have kids I do I have a daughter
and are you
married no so with your with your
daughter so you being a single parent uh
such as myself like what's your what's
your goal for your daughter like in
terms of like what's your your vision
for your for your for your
child um I want to be able to provide
the means to to uh attack whatever
opportunities in life that she finds for
herself um and with that comes a strong
work ethic and a sense of
responsibility so she's 12 years
old and this summer she starts working
for Titans
electrical um
wow she's she's uh she's coming in the
office for two days a week for her
summer she's giving me two days a week
I'm paying her
and uh we're going to start teaching her
man so that my hope is that when she's
18 and she gets out of high school and
she's an adult uh that she's got a mean
work ethic and she can apply it to
whatever Choice she makes in her own
life M that's awesome man and um
if if someone had to tell your
legacy what would they
say now or like like 50 years from now
5050 years it don't matter time there's
no time or space like if someone were to
talk about your legacy and what would
they
say that dude genuinely cared for
people that dude gave of
hisself and that dude helped out a lot
of a lot of people man that's that's my
hope at my funeral I hope somebody
stands up there and says hey that dude
that dude helped that dude touched that
dude gave and uh if I can live up to
that standard uh then then I consider it
success now
um when it comes
to things that make you angry what are
the things that make you angry and it
could be anything like people that drive
on the left side of the road I don't
know what are the things that make you
angry man Injustice man uh
people who take advantage of uh of other
people people who take advantage of of
children you know I'm I'm a Libertarian
man I'm a firm believer that I don't
care what you do as long as it doesn't
impede on on what I'm doing you know
you're an adult make adult decisions for
yourself man uh but when you bring kids
in the mix man you know that's uh that's
horrible I these these new Facebook
lives that are coming out here in
Memphis at a IH hop this past week man
uh this dude was was choking out this
girl and instead of stopping it somebody
decided to go live on Facebook with it
and a man tried to break it up and when
the man tried to break it up the other
guy turned around and killed him right
there on Facebook live man so it the
desensitivity that that we uh just
accept in this day and time is is is
terrible man so Injustice I hate
Injustice wow how are you with money and
I mean I don't mean to just jump without
the segue I like you know this is like
the the lightning round questions but
like before I I go into that and I'm you
know it's just force of habit but you
know I I'm seeing a lot of that I was
just talking to somebody in regards to
um you know just letting my kid play
certain games like we're we're growing
into a nation where people are so
desensitized you know to what they're
starting to see in terms of violence
they just think that violence is okay
it's it's an everyday thing you know
we're in the now but we're not really
thinking about the consequences of the
future so you know I'm really really
sorry to hear you know that happening in
your neck of the woods and I and and I
hope that you know in the future that
you know our children can grow up in
into uh a a a time where people care
about each other again like when we were
growing up you know so it's really
really really really sad to hear that so
I didn't mean to folks I didn't mean to
segue into that it's just force a habit
but like it honestly I hate when I see
stuff like that and and
um but uh when it comes to like have you
like are you following the black lives
matter movement and and whatnot um have
you have you seen some of those kids
being shot on the um you know on
Facebook not Facebook live but like
what's your views on on that you talking
about uh with with police now that we
have live video and yeah CU because you
were talking about you know um Injustice
and and and whatnot like are you
speaking of some of those events as
well all Injustice really but when you
ask me that question what's the one
thing that makes me angry man it's uh
it's it's Injustice to kids but to speak
on the black lives matter uh
deal not so much about the movement but
the act that brings about the
movement yeah man I I mean I think
there's a lot of uh police officers out
here that are great I think there's also
a lot of police officers out here that
carry a grudge and are used to nobody
watching over them and so they're able
to kind of kind of Swing the swing the
big stick around and and treat people
however they want to I I uh I I was
exposed to that when I was younger you
know like I told you I grew up uh as a
minority out west and so when I moved
back here um I would experience when I
was riding around with with black people
and the cops pull us over we're treated
way different I mean riding around with
white kids man we get pulled over we're
drunk we got weed in the
car cops are like hey man just uh just
go sit on that stool over there and and
sober up and then go home you know get
pulled over black folks don't have
nothing in the car get jerked out the
car man uh you know kicking my legs
apart and and so I experiened the the
difference there but I think it's a uh
per case deal man we can't blanket over
it man you can't just say you know all
cops hate black people or you know all
black people hate police or all white
people hate you know those blanket
statements are really uh unjustified in
this situation man there's there's
doctors that that do messed up uh
there's TV hosts that do messed up
there's preachers that do messed up
so you know it's a case by casee
situation man yes there's cops out there
yes there's cops that pull their gun
before they should and yes we're seeing
more of that because of the the video
element you know but I think some of
that stuff is Justified it's cool I mean
none nothing's cool about it but it is
neat for us to have video to see you
know it becomes it's crazy to me how
people still argue about it when it is
on video you say hey in this particular
case this dude dude was just doing this
and all of a sudden this happened you
know and we've got we've it's not just
hearsay we have a video to see it now um
but yeah any Injustice man what do you
think about politics like do you follow
politics are you into um what's
happening right now because there seems
to be a lot of now um there seems to be
a lot of drama happening on CNN Fox News
in regards to Trump Russia and and
whatnot that do you follow politics at
all dude I I don't watch TV at all I
don't even have a TV in my house anymore
um so I used to follow politics heavy uh
2012 election iass said I'm libertarian
man so I was I was Ron Paul all the way
what what I'm libertarian too hey hey
hey look at us yeah um two minorities
here on the hustle
Zone libertarian selves um
but as I realized or what I learned and
my beliefs in our political system are
that there's so much stuff that goes on
behind closed doors there's so much big
money that changes hands there's so much
with lobbyist and and and the real issue
is inside Congress man I really believe
that there are people who go into
congress with with a firm belief that
they're going to change Washington and
at the end of the day man Washington
changes them man uh they stay there too
long and they're surrounded by evil and
whatever their Vice is man it's served
on a hot plate right there in front of
them that's right if if I can get your
vote you can have this whatever this may
be man uh whatever whatever's hard for
you to turn down is standing right there
at your door every time you come home
and you know you can fight it for a year
or two or three or four you're in there
for 20 years man Washington changes you
you don't go and change Washington and
that's what I really liked about Ron
Paul yeah he was the same dude at the
beginning of his uh
in as the beginning of his stin in
Congress as he was when he left and he's
still that same guy now man he you go
back and look man it had be like one
vote versus everybody else in Congress
so he'd be that one guy voting on his
own he just he was not uh he didn't give
up to the pressure man and I got to
commend him for that because everybody
else does everybody else gets gets
molded uh in some shape or form but I
feel like there's so much that goes on
on the backstory I feel like they put a
puppet in front of us uh for us to argue
and complain about you know oh Trump
this Trump that man like Les Brown said
man don't worry about the White House
worry about your house you know because
what Trump is doing is not affecting me
in my everyday grind and that goes for
uh for Obama and and him too you know
what Obama was doing you know there's
nothing I could do to change it I could
get mad about what Obama did I could get
mad about what Trump did at the end of
the day man what can I do but just put
my face down go back to work and make my
life as good as I can make it here for
me that's awesome I mean uh I just you
know sorry for all the questions uh but
this is the hustle Zone man we I talk
about everything because it's not just
about you grinding every day Hustle Hard
motivate you know it's it's about who
who are you as a person you know and I
try to get so many people from so many
different backgrounds and and I I you
know I want to hear everything now um
closing closing this out what what's the
number one book that you recommend for
somebody to read are we talking about
somebody who's never picked up a book in
their life or somebody that's well
versed dictionary I want you to read
that dictionary you need to learn how to
read
um uh let's see no how about I just
cover it instead of keeping asking you
me coming back and asking you questions
let me let me just cover cover the bases
man okay uh I
like seller be so Grant Cardone
I
like Relentless Tim
Grover and right now I'm in the middle
of Extreme ownership by Joo about the
Navy Seals um and that really uh I can
resonate with that uh not to that
extreme I'm not saying I'm a Navy SEAL
by any means man them dudes are beast
but the way that he leads uh I mean I
can pull a lot from extreme ownership
you know there's no excuses if it
happens on my watch if it happens in my
company if it happens while you're here
with me then I get all the blame and
that's if it's good that's if it's bad
that's if it's horrible you know uh it's
on me I'm the leader so it all comes it
all falls in my lap and and I have to
take the take the full responsibility
extreme
ownership that's awesome so folks um and
so uh Jason where can we find
you man uh I'm I'm very active on
Facebook Hey I just struck up my YouTube
but I can't tell you how to find me on
YouTube because apparently you got to
have a bunch of followers before they
let you actually put your name in there
so it's like YouTube xy3 zfp you know
something crazy find me on Facebook or
find me on Instagram and uh those are
the two platforms that I'm extremely
active on that's awesome and um apart
from the uh technical difficulties it
was all over the place uh what how did
you feel about the uh being on the
hustles home for the first time man I'm
I'm looking forward to being a regular
man I I like it the uh the questions are
engaging and I tell you what I'm really
looking forward to I'm looking forward
to the roles being reversed and you
coming on home with a hustle for Mr
Monday night and letting the Titan pick
your brain well I'm I'm so down I'm so
down I got you know most people don't
invite me on their shows so like I but I
got a lot to say man there's all kinds
of stories and and and whatnot so I'd be
happy to be on your show well we're
going to be strategic about that man
we're going to we're we're going to know
exactly when all this stuff is popping
off and we're going to we're going to
bring you on and and really shine that
light on what me and you are doing
together not just in the hustle Zone but
outside of that with the website and and
Ryan's going to help me with my YouTube
presence and man me and Ryan are going
to do some work together man I really
appreciate you man I'm glad we linked up
uh Crystal's Crystal's great man she's
she has made some really solid moves for
me man if she points somebody out to me
and says you need to talk to that guy
100% of the time it's somebody that I
need to talk to man she doesn't play Big
up to Crystal Jones I mean crystal is um
she's a mover and Shaker and that's why
I like her and I think that um and and
there's a lot of people that I'm going
to be introducing um to all of you um in
terms of uh people that are going to be
writers and content creators they're all
solid people um I I'm so um blessed and
and highly favored for all of the the
the people that wanted to volunteer
their time
um to put this all together because we
all see a need to you know unveil the
culture of entrepreneurialism so there's
a tradition on every hustle
Z and
um and I'm going to get you to to
continue on with this
tradition all right so I'm going to do
well you know what a call and responses
because you're an MC so from a MC to a
fellow MC um when I say
hustle oh sorry when I say welcome to
the I want you to say hustle Zone but
you got to scream it loud as you can and
I'm not going to let go until you
actually do it loud you got to do it
like crazy loud and then we're and this
is our sign off this is the sign off
so welcome to the hustle
Zone there you go I love it I love it
thank you guys thank you so much and
folks um man I I every every time we do
the hustle Zone it gets better and
better and again I apologize for um the
technical difficulties uh sometimes we
get it right sometimes we don't this was
one of the nights where we did not get
it right uh but you know regardless of
the technical difficulties we had really
good quality person come on to the show
uh Jason is pretty awesome you know
being a guy that paved his own way he's
always wanted to do his own thing and
now you know being such an inspiration
to so many people like you know I tagged
him in a post yesterday and all the
people all of his people just swarmed in
and supported him and just they like
what he's doing because he gives us such
a positive vibe and positive energy so
I'm so happy to have him here and and
folks you know like like all the
entrepreneurs that come on this show we
don't quit we don't give up we just move
forward and so I wish uh I wish you guys
all the best thank you guys for
supporting the hustle Zone make make
sure you guys pick up your um your uh
your t-shirts and and and and whatnot to
support the show and it's a hustle
hustle hustle zone. clo uh the other
thing too is u i put all the links in
the description so um please like us
support us share this out uh you know
get get us into the uh into everyone's
timelines um not because I'm Ryan Perez
but because you get to hear another side
of the hustle that's how you differenti
the hustle Zone from every other hustle
zone is or every other you know um show
is that we really focus on the person um
and not necessarily you know the ego or
what Puffs them up you know we want to
know the The Human Side so that we can
get a better understanding of what makes
them tick so um I again I want to thank
Jason Daniels and all the supporters
tonight I'm sorry I couldn't display
your your um your your comments there's
just a bug in the system and it's
affecting everything
so um I have to get that all figured out
so that next time that it's a Flawless
show so thank you guys so much and uh
much love